Guide to the Savage Mining Company and Associated Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Executive Records, 1858-1959; Series I; 15; (11 boxes)
  - GENERAL RECORDS
    - State of Nevada, District Courts 1st and 3rd
      - Thomas Bell vs. Humboldt Mining Company, [1890] (Box 8, Folder 125)
      - Supreme Council of Chosen Friends vs. Wilhelmina Biter, William Brown, Anna Francesca Brown, 1893 Aug 21 (Box 8, Folder 126)
      - Thomas McNamara and Michael McNamara vs. R. P. Keating and R. Pendergast, 1895 Aug 28 (Box 8, Folder 127)
      - Frank A. Wilder vs. John Drynen et. al. (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - State of Nevada, Supreme Court
      - Thomas McNamara Jr. et. al. vs. R. P. Keating et. al., n.d. (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - United States Circuit Court, 9th cir., Nevada
      - William B. Thornburgh vs. Savage Mining Company, 1867 (Box 8, Folder 130-40)
        This material has been microfilmed and is represented here by copyflow produced from the film. Call number of film: MS Vault / Microfilm / 674.
      - William B. Thornburgh vs. Savage Mining Company, 1867 (Box 9, Folder 141-54)
      - William B. Thornburgh vs. Savage Mining Company, 1867 (Box 10, Folder 155)
      - Thomas Bell vs. Humboldt Mining Company, R. P. Keating, R. Pendergast, William H. Watson, and Thomas McNamara, [1890] (Box 10, Folder 156)
      - Thomas Bell vs. Bailey Mining Company, R. P. Keating, R. Pendergast, William H. Watson, and Thomas McNamara, 1890 Jul 22 (Box 10, Folder 157)
      - United States of America vs. Jewett William Adams, Robert P. Keating, Joseph Bernard Mallon, 1891 Apr 28 (Box 10, Folder 158)
      - Joseph M. Douglass vs. James D. Byrnes, et. al., n.d. (Box 10, Folder 159)
    - City & County San Francisco, Superior Court
      - Robert P. Keating vs. [George] T. J. Coultier, 1888 Dec 18 (Box 10, Folder 160)
      - H. M. Levy vs. George T. Coulter, 1888, 1890 (Box 10, Folder 161)
      - Estate of George T. Coulter, 1892 (Box 10, Folder 162)
  - BOWERS COMPANY
    - [Share account], 1860-62 (Box 10a, Folder 163)
    - [Share account], n.d. (Box 10, Folder 164)
  - BULLION GOLD AND SILVER MINING COMPANY
    - Stock journal, 1906-18 (Box 10b, Folder 165)
  - CHOLLAR GOLD AND SILVER MINING COMPANY
    - By-laws, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 166)
  - [EUGENE DEWEY, STOCKBROKER]
    - [Stock account ledger for R. P. Keating], 1877-79 (Box 10c, Folder 167)
  - GOLDEN EAGLE MINING COMPANY
    - Application for patent for Northern Belle No. 2 Mining Claim, 1891 (Box 10, Folder 168)
  - GOULD AND CURRY MINING COMPANY
    - Minutes from the annual stockholders meeting and the board of directors meeting (printed in Daily Exchange ), 1882 Dec 19 (Box 10, Folder 169)
    - Certificate ledger (S & T ledger), 1906-07 (Box 10d, Folder 170)
    - Stock ledger, 1907-11 (Box 10e, Folder 171)
    - Assessment roll [ledger], 1911-25 (Box 10f, Folder 172)
    - Assessment book [daybook], 1912-17 (Box 10g, Folder 173)
  - HALE & NORCROSS SILVER MINING COMPANY
    - Notice of annual stockholders meeting, 1890 Mar (Box 10, Folder 174)
    - Letters from the superintendent, 1866 (Box 10h, Folder 175)
      This is a letterpress copybook.
    - Letters from the superintendent, 1869-75
      - Letterpress copybook (Box 10i, Folder 176)
      - Letterpress copybook (Box 10j, Folder 177)
    - Insurance policy on mine buildings and equipment, 1875 Oct 24 (Box 10, Folder 178)
  - HIGHLAND MARY MINING COMPANY
    - Minutes of a stockholder meeting, 1881 Jun 21 (Box 10, Folder 179)
  - HILLSIDE WATER COMPANY
    - Form for interest in stock, 1891 (Box 10, Folder 180)
    - Maps, notes, and papers regarding water and land claims, [1889], n.d. (Box 10, Folder 181)
      See also: Oversize, Box 82, folder 1401
    - Memoranda regarding Gov. Adams visit to Inyo, 1893 Mar (Box 10, Folder 182)
    - Notes regarding fruit trees, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 183)
  - R.P.K. [R. P. KEATING] & CO.
    - Rec'd and del'd [receipts and delivery], 1874-[76] (Box 10k, Folder 184)
  - [SAMUEL DIXON, STOCKBROKER]
    - [Stock account book for R. P. Keating], 1872-74 (Box 10l, Folder 185)
  - SAVAGE MINING COMPANY
    - Certificate of incorporation (1862 Oct 14): copy, 1864 Mar 8 (Box 10, Folder 186)
    - Minutes from the annual stockholders meeting and the board of directors meetings, 1906-20 (Box 10m, Folder 187)
    - Minutes from the annual stockholders meeting and the board of directors meetings, 1906-20 (Box 10, Folder 188)
    - Resolutions and memoranda, 1862,1882,n.d. (Box 10, Folder 189)
    - Affidavits of annual labor performed by Savage Mining Company, 1897 Dec (Box 10, Folder 190)
    - Annual report: drafts and notes, 1866 (Box 10, Folder 191)
    - Annual report: drafts and notes, 1875 (Box 10, Folder 192)
    - Annual report: drafts and notes, 1884 (Box 10, Folder 193)
    - Annual report: drafts and notes, 1885 (Box 10, Folder 193a)
    - Annual report: drafts and notes, 1886 (Box 10, Folder 194)
    - Annual report: drafts and notes, 1888 (Box 10, Folder 195)
    - Annual report: drafts and notes, 1889 (Box 10, Folder 196)
    - Annual report: drafts and notes, 1892 (Box 10, Folder 197)
    - Annual report: drafts and notes, 1896 (Box 10, Folder 198)
    - Annual report: miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 199)
    - Letters to the Executive, 1866-1932 (Box 11, Folder 200)
    - Letters from the superintendent, 1863-65 (Box 11a, Folder 201)
    - Letters from the superintendent, 1868-71
      - Letterpress copybook (Box 11b, Folder 202)
      - Letterpress copybook (Box 11c, Folder 203)
      - Letterpress copybook (Box 11d, Folder 204)
      - Letterpress copybook (Box 11e, Folder 205)
    - Letters from the superintendent, 1873-77 (Box 11f, Folder 206)
    - Insurance policies on superintendent's office and dwelling, 1866-90 (Box 11, Folder 207-208)
      See also: Oversize, Box 82, folder 1402
    - Miscellaneous notes, [1864]-89 (Box 11, Folder 209)
    - Photographs of superintendent's office and dwelling, 1959 Nov (Box 11, Folder 210)
  - SOUTH COMSTOCK CONSOLIDATED MINING COMPANY
    - Depositions regarding mining claims, 1885 Jun-Jul (Box 11, Folder 211)
  - T. H. RALSTON, STOCKBROKER
    - Order book, 1877-70 (Box 11g, Folder 212)
  - WASHOE MONTE CARLO COPPER COMPANY
    - Minutes of the board of directors meetings, 1906-07 (Box 11h, Folder 213)
  - UNIDENTIFIED COMPANIES
    - Minutes of a meeting, 1861 Jul 27 (Box 11, Folder 214)
    - Miscellaneous, 1865-88, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 215)
  - UNIDENTIFIED STOCKBROKERS
    - Order book, 1876-1877 (Box 11i, Folder 216)
    - Stocks belonging to our clients, 1875 Mar (Box 11, Folder 217)
    - Miscellaneous notes, 1881-94, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 218-19)
- Operation Records, 1866-1902; Series II; 10; (15 boxes)
  Series II, Operation Records, is arranged alphabetically by company name. Material whose corporate origin can not be identified has been placed at the end.
  - ATCHISON MILL
    - Monthly reports of operations, 1866-69
      See: Savage monthly reports of operations, Box 13, folders 256-58
    - Weekly report, 1867 Jun 29 (Box 12, Folder 220)
    - Weekly reports of ore production and expenses, 1866-69
      See: Savage weekly reports of ore production and expenses, Box 13, folders 256-258
  - CHOLLAR MILL
    - Daily report, 1890 Feb 24 (Box 12, Folder 220a)
  - CHOLLAR-NORCROSS-SAVAGE SHAFT CO.
    - Statement of operations, 1880-86
      See: Oversize, Box 83-84, folders 1403-09
  - CROWN POINT MINING COMPANY
    - General report, 1880 (Box 12, Folder 221)
  - HALE & NORCROSS MINING COMPANY
    - Yearly report of mining operations, 1882 (Box 12, Folder 222)
    - Weekly reports of operations, 1873, 1882 (Box 12, Folder 223)
    - Weekly reports of operations, 1886-87 (Box 12, Folder 224)
    - Weekly reports of operations, 1891-93
      See: Savage Weekly reports, Box 14-15, folders 280-83, 290
    - Daily reports of operations, 1873-87 (Box 12a, Folder 225)
    - Daily reports of operations, 1873-87 (Box 12b, Folder 226)
    - Daily reports of operations, 1873-87 (Box 12c, Folder 227)
    - Daily shift boss reports, 1883-86 (Box 12d, Folder 228)
    - Daily shift boss reports, 1883-86 (Box 12e, Folder 229)
    - Daily shift boss reports, 1883-86 (Box 12f, Folder 230)
    - Daily shift boss reports, 1883-86 (Box 12g, Folder 231)
    - Daily shift boss reports, 1884 (Box 12, Folder 232)
    - Daily reports from Empire Mill, 1889 (Box 12, Folder 233-35)
    - Daily reports from Mexican Mill, 1889-90 (Box 12, Folder 236-37)
    - Daily cards from Mexican Mill, 1891 (Box 12, Folder 238-39)
    - Weekly/Monthly report from Nevada Mill, 1892, 1894-95
      See: Savage Nevada Mill reports, Box 25, folder 361-63
    - Weekly reports from Sutro Tunnel Company, 1891-93
      See: Savage weekly reports from the Sutro Tunnel Company, Box 24a, folders 358a-f
    - General daycards, 1871,1887-97,n.d.
      See: Savage General daycards, Boxes 20-24, folders 351-58
  - JUSTICE MINING COMPANY
    - Weekly reports, 1894-95
      See: Savage Weekly reports, Boxes 16-17, folders 302-16
  - SAVAGE MINING COMPANY
    - Savage Mine
      - Yearly reports of operations, 1882 (Box 12, Folder 240)
      - Yearly reports of operations, 1887-96 (Box 12, Folder 241-250)
      - Yearly reports of operations, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 251-253)
      - Monthly reports of operations, 1864 Oct (Box 13, Folder 254)
      - Monthly reports of operations, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 255)
      - Monthly reports of operations, 1866-69 (Box 13a, Folder 256)
      - Monthly reports of operations, 1866-69 (Box 13b, Folder 257)
      - Monthly reports of operations, 1866-69 (Box 13c, Folder 258)
      - Weekly reports of ore production and expenses, 1865
        See: Oversize, Box 92, folder 1463
      - Weekly reports of ore production and expenses, 1869-70
        See: Oversize, Boxes 92-93, folder 1464-69
      - Weekly reports of operations, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 259)
      - Weekly reports of operations, 1868-70 (Box 13, Folder 260-262)
      - Weekly reports of operations, 1876 (Box 13, Folder 263)
      - Weekly reports of operations, 1887-88 (Box 13, Folder 264-270)
      - Weekly reports of operations, 1889-92 (Box 14, Folder 271-282)
      - Weekly reports of operations, 1892-94 Aug (Box 15, Folder 283-294)
      - Weekly reports of operations, 1892-94 Aug (Box 16, Folder 295-307)
      - Weekly reports of operations, 1894 Sep-95,n.d. (Box 17, Folder 308-316)
      - Weekly reports of operations, 1894 Sep-95,n.d (Box 17a, Folder 317)
      - Weekly reports of operations, 1894 Sep-95,n.d (Box 17, Folder 318-319)
      - Daily reports of operations, 1875-76 Oct (Box 17, Folder 320-26)
      - Daily reports of operations, 1876 Nov-77 (Box 18, Folder 327-29)
      - Daily reports of operations, 1884 (Box 18a, Folder 330)
      - Daily shift boss reports, 1881 (Box 18, Folder 331)
      - Daily shift boss reports, 1884 (Box 18, Folder 332)
      - Monthly reports of material consumed, 1868-69
        See: Oversize, Box 84, folder 1410
      - Daily reports of material used, 1887 Mar (Box 18, Folder 333)
      - Report of material used in building new hoisting works, 1874-75, n.d.
        See: Oversize, Box 84, folder 1411
      - Daily pump reports, 1877-80 (Box 18b, Folder 334)
      - Reports of Men Employed
        - Weekly, 1894-97, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 335-38)
        - Daily, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 339)
      - General daybook, 1873 (Box 19, Folder 340)
      - General daybook, 1883 (Box 19, Folder 341)
      - General daybooks, 1887-89 (Box 19, Folder 342)
      - General daybooks, 1887-89 (Box 19a, Folder 343)
      - General daycards, 1871 (Box 20, Folder 344)
      - General daycards, 1887-90 (Box 20, Folder 345-348)
      - General daycards, 1890-97, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 349-350)
      - General daycards, 1890-97, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 351)
      - General daycards, 1890-97, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 351a-352)
      - General daycards, 1890-97, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 353-358)
    - Mill and Sutro Tunnel Company Reports
      - Weekly reports from Sutro Tunnel Company, 1891-93 (Box 24a, Folder 358a-f)
      - Weekly/Monthly report from Nevada Mill, 1889-90 (Box 25, Folder 359-360)
      - Weekly/Monthly report from Nevada Mill, 1892 (Box 25, Folder 361)
      - Weekly/Monthly report from Nevada Mill, 1894-95 (Box 25, Folder 362-363)
      - Daily report from Rock Point Mill, 1888-90, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 364-384)
      - Report of ore delivered to Santiago Mill, 1882 (Box 25, Folder 385)
      - Report of ore delivered to Sapphire Mill, Aug (Box 25, Folder 386)
      - Savage Mill monthly reports of operations, 1866 (Box 25, Folder 387)
        See also: Box 13, folders 256-58
  - SCORPION MINING COMPANY
    - Weekly reports of operations, 1891-94
      See: Savage Weekly reports, Box 14-15, folders 274-83, Box 16, folders 302-06.
  - UNIDENTIFIED OPERATION REPORTS
    - Reports of operations, 1884, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 388)
      See also: Oversize, Box 94, folder 1470
    - Maps of the mine levels, 1887, n.d.
      See: Oversize, Box 94, folder 1471
- Ore and Bullion Records, 1863-1914; Series III; 18.5; (17 boxes)
  Series III, Ore and Bullion Records, is arranged alphabetically by company name. Within each company, ore books (the fullest account of ore production) are placed first, followed by bullion and ore assays. Unidentified records have been placed at the end.
  - CHOLLAR GOLD AND SILVER MINING COMPANY
    - Ore assay report, 1895 May 2 (Box 26, Folder 389)
  - CONSOLIDATED CALIFORNIA & VIRGINIA MINING COMPANY
    - Memorandum of bullion, 1886 May 12 (Box 26, Folder 389a)
    - Ore assay reports, 1886 (Box 26, Folder 390)
    - Ore assay reports, 1893-94 (Box 26, Folder 391-392)
  - HALE and NORCROSS MINING COMPANY
    - Ore book, 1866-74, 1884 (Box 26a, Folder 393)
    - Ore book, 1866-74, 1884 (Box 26b, Folder 394)
    - Ore book, 1866-74, 1884 (Box 26c, Folder 395)
    - Ore book, 1889-90
      See: Savage Ore book, Box 27, folder 439
    - Bullion accounts, 1868-71,1884-85 (Box 26d, Folder 396)
    - Bullion accounts, 1888, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 397)
    - Memoranda of bullion, 1888 (Box 26, Folder 398)
    - Ore assay reports, 1881 (Box 26, Folder 399)
    - Ore assay reports, 1883-84 (Box 26, Folder 400)
    - Ore assay reports, 1886-88 Jul (Box 26, Folder 401-408)
    - Ore assay reports, 1888-91 (Box 26e, Folder 409-415)
    - Ore assay reports, 1891-92, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 416-422)
    - Statements for the Sutro Tunnel Company, 1884-89 (Box 27, Folder 423-424)
    - Statement of ore weighed, 1884, 1888 (Box 27, Folder 425)
    - Miscellaneous, 1888, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 426)
  - JUSTICE MINING COMPANY
    - Ore assay reports, 1878 (Box 27, Folder 427)
    - Ore assay reports, 1893-94 (Box 27, Folder 428-433)
  - SAVAGE MINING COMPANY
    - Ore book, 1863-65 (Box 27a, Folder 434)
    - Ore book, 1863-65 (Box 27b, Folder 435)
    - Ore book [individual pages], 1866 (Box 27, Folder 436)
    - Ore book, 1869-73 (Box 27c, Folder 437)
    - Ore book, 1886-1896 (Box 27d, Folder 438)
    - Ore book, 1888-1896 (Box 27e, Folder 439)
    - Memoranda of Bullion
      - G. W. Bell, 1863-64 (Box 27, Folder 440-447)
      - Theall & Co., 1864-68 (Box 27, Folder 448-452)
      - Van Wyck & Co., 1864 (Box 27, Folder 453-455a)
      - Van Wyck & Co., 1865-66 (Box 28, Folder 456-460)
      - Gould and Curry, 1866-67, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 461)
        See also: Oversize, Box 85, folders 1412-1413
      - Savage, [1868]-70
        See: Oversize, Box 85, folders 1414-16
      - Savage, 1871-73 (Box 28, Folder 462-473)
      - E. Ruhling & Co., 1870 (Box 28, Folder 474)
      - U. S. Mint, 1892 (Box 28, Folder 475-476)
      - Shelby Smelting & Lead Co., 1895 Nov 14 (Box 28, Folder 477)
    - Ore assay reports, 1863 (Box 28, Folder 478)
    - Ore assay reports, 1866-68 (Box 28, Folder 479-487)
    - Ore assay reports, 1870 (Box 29, Folder 488-490)
    - Ore assay reports, 1878 (Box 29, Folder 491-492)
    - Ore assay reports, 1881 (Box 29, Folder 493-495)
    - Ore assay reports, 1883-84 (Box 29, Folder 496-497)
    - Ore assay reports, 1886-88 (Box 29, Folder 498-515)
    - Ore assay reports, 1888 (Box 30, Folder 516-523)
    - Ore assay reports, 1888-89 (Box 31, Folder 524-533)
    - Ore assay reports, 1889-90 (Box 32, Folder 534-547)
    - Ore assay reports, 1890 (Box 33, Folder 548-554)
    - Ore assay reports, 1890-91 (Box 34, Folder 555-564)
    - Ore assay reports, 1891 (Box 35, Folder 565-574)
    - Ore assay reports, 1891 (Box 36, Folder 575-583)
    - Ore assay reports, 1891-92 (Box 37, Folder 584-592)
    - Ore assay reports, 1892 (Box 38, Folder 593-596e)
    - Ore assay reports, 1892-93 (Box 39, Folder 597-609)
    - Ore assay reports, 1893-95 (Box 40, Folder 610-626)
    - Ore assay reports, 1895 (Box 41, Folder 627-628)
    - Ore assay reports, 1914, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 628a-629)
    - Assays of Ore per Samples
      - Ledgers: samples from wagons, 1867-71 (Box 41a, Folder 630)
      - Ledgers: samples from wagons, 1867-71 (Box 41b, Folder 631)
      - Ledger: samples from pulp at Mills, 1867-70 (Box 41c, Folder 632)
      - Summaries of wagon and pulp samples, 1867-70 (Box 41, Folder 633)
        See: Oversize, Box 86, folder 1417
      - [Daybook]: Island Mill wagon samples, 1867 (Box 41d, Folder 634)
      - [Daybook]: car samples, 1891 Nov 14 (Box 41, Folder 635)
      - [Daybook]: car samples, 1891-1897 (Box 41e, Folder 636)
      - [Daybook]: car samples, 1892
        See: Oversize, Box 86, folder 1418
      - Dump samples: list of sample markings, 1869-70 (Box 41, Folder 637)
    - Assay calculations: Grants' notes evaluating the ore, 1889-90 (Box 41, Folder 638)
    - Statements for Sutro Tunnel Co., 1880-88 (Box 41, Folder 639)
    - Statements for Sutro Tunnel Co., 1890-96
      See: Oversize, Box 86, folder 1419
    - Ore shipped from mine--bullion rec'd and shipped to San Francisco, 1866 (Box 41, Folder 640)
      See also: Oversize, Box 86, 1420
    - Ore shipped from mine--bullion rec'd and shipped to San Francisco, 1866-69 (Box 41f, Folder 641)
    - Ore shipped from mine--bullion rec'd and shipped to San Francisco, 1866-69 (Box 41g, Folder 642)
    - Bullion shipped to San Francisco, 1868-69
      See: Oversize, Box 86, folder 1421
    - Ore accounts: reporting mine levels ore hoisted from, 1891-93 (Box 41, Folder 643)
    - Statements of ore weighed at railroad scales, shipped from mine to mills, 1870-89 (Box 41, Folder 644-646)
    - Miscellaneous, 1865-66, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 647)
  - SCORPION MINING COMPANY
    - Ore assay report, 1878 Feb 28 (Box 41, Folder 648)
  - SIERRA NEVADA MINING COMPANY
    - Ore assay report, 1892 Sep 3 (Box 41, Folder 649)
  - UNIDENTIFIED ORE RECORDS
    - Memorandum of bullion, 1889 Aug 8 (Box 41, Folder 650)
    - Ore assay reports: [daybook of various mine samples], 1874-75 (Box 41h, Folder 651)
    - Ore assay reports: [daybook of various mine samples], 1874-75 (Box 41i, Folder 652)
    - Ore assay reports: [daybook of various mine samples], 1874-75 (Box 41j, Folder 653)
    - Ore assay reports: [daybook of various mine samples], 1874-75 (Box 41k, Folder 654)
    - Ore assay reports: [daybook of various mine samples], 1874-75 (Box 41l, Folder 655)
    - Ore assay reports: [daybook of various mine samples], 1874-75 (Box 41m, Folder 656)
    - Ore assay reports, 1871-89, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 657)
      See also: Oversize, Box 86, folder 1422
    - Average value of car and battery samples per ton, 1887-90 (Box 41, Folder 658)
    - Ore reduced at Mills, 1869 May (Box 41, Folder 659)
    - Miscellaneous, 1870,1883,n.d. (Box 41, Folder 660)
- Financial Records, 1860-1942; Series IV; 33.5; (21 boxes)
  Series IV, Financial Records, is arranged alphabetically by company name. The arrangement within each company follows the pattern: ledgers, cashbooks, daybooks, accounts, and receipts. Material whose corporate origin can not be identified has been placed at the end.
  - ALABAMA MINING COMPANY
    - Receipt, 1889 Sep 30 (Box 42, Folder 661)
  - ATCHISON MILL
    - Receipts, 1866-69 (Box 42, Folder 662)
  - BOWERS COMPANY
    - Accounts, 1860-62, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 663-665)
  - BRUNSWICK EXPLORATION COMPANY
    - Report of receipts and disbursements, 1896, 1899 (Box 42, Folder 666)
  - CHOLLAR MINING COMPANY
    - Ledger, 1889-1909 (Box 42a, Folder 667)
  - CHOLLAR-NORCROSS-SAVAGE SHAFT CO.
    - Statement of disbursements and superintendent's account, 1878-92 (Box 42, Folder 668-682)
    - Statement of disbursements and superintendent's account, 1894-1901 (Box 42, Folder 683-690)
    - Joint expenses of Hale & Norcross Mining Company and Savage Mining Company, 1881-83 (Box 43, Folder 691)
    - Miscellaneous accounts, 1886 (Box 43, Folder 692)
    - Receipts, 1881-87 (Box 43, Folder 693)
  - CONSOLIDATED CALIFORNIA & VIRGINIA MINING COMPANY
    - Receipt, 1886 May 12 (Box 43, Folder 694)
  - D. G. M. [COMPANY]
    - Bank records: check stubs, 1875-1901 (Box 43a, Folder 695)
  - GOLDEN EAGLE AND ISIS TUNNEL COMPANY
    - Receipts, 1893 Apr (Box 43, Folder 696)
  - GOULD AND CURRY MINING COMPANY
    - Ledger, 1909-33 (Box 43b, Folder 697)
    - Miscellaneous accounts, 1876, 1886 (Box 43, Folder 698)
    - Receipt, 1867 Apr 26 (Box 43, Folder 699)
  - HALE & NORCROSS MINING COMPANY
    - Cashbooks, 1868-82 (Box 43c, Folder 700)
    - Cashbooks, 1868-82 (Box 43d, Folder 701)
    - Statement of receipts and disbursements, 1882-87,1890 (Box 43, Folder 702-707)
    - President in account with superintendent, 1888, 1890
      See: Oversize, Box 87, folder 1423
    - Pump expense
      See: Savage pump expense, Box 44, folder 757
    - Miscellaneous accounts, 1880-90 (Box 43, Folder 708)
      See also: Savage, miscellaneous accounts, Box 61, folder 1024-25
    - Receipts, 1867-90,n.d. (Box 43, Folder 709-713)
  - HILLSIDE WATER COMPANY
    - [Accounts], 1891-94 (Box 43, Folder 714)
    - Drafts issued to date, 1888-89 (Box 43, Folder 715-716)
    - Expenses, 1888 (Box 43, Folder 717)
    - Receipts, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 718)
  - HOOSIER STATE MILL
    - Cashbook, 1872-73 (Box 43e, Folder 719)
    - Bank records: checks, 1873 (Box 43, Folder 720)
  - JUSTICE MINING COMPANY
    - Bank records, Nevada Bank of San Francisco, Virginia City: check stubs, 1893-94 (Box 43, Folder 721)
    - Receipts, 1894 (Box 43, Folder 722)
  - LADY BRYAN MINING COMPANY
    - Receipts, 1876-77,1882 (Box 44, Folder 723-725)
      See also: Oversize, Box 87, folder 1424
  - LADY WASHINGTON MINING COMPANY
    - Receipt, 1877 Apr 30 (Box 44, Folder 726)
  - M. [MONAHAN] & COMPANY
    - Ledger, 1879-80 (Box 44a, Folder 727)
    - Cashbook, 1879-80 (Box 44b, Folder 728)
  - M & H COMPANY
    - Ledger, 1874-75 (Box 44c, Folder 729)
  - OCCIDENTAL MILL
    - Receipts, 1871 (Box 44, Folder 730)
  - PLESS D. & R. COMPANY
    - Bank records, Bank of California, Virginia City: bank book, 1894-96 (Box 44, Folder 731)
  - R.P.K. [R. P. KEATING] & COMPANY
    - Ledger, 1876-77 (Box 44d, Folder 732)
    - Index to ledger, [1876-77] (Box 44e, Folder 733)
    - R. P. Keating in account with company, 1874-75 (Box 44, Folder 734)
  - SAVAGE MILL
    - Accounts, 1866, 1871, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 735)
  - SAVAGE MINING COMPANY
    - General Records
      - Ledgers, 1862-71 (Box 44f, Folder 736)
      - Ledgers, 1862-71 (Box 44g, Folder 737)
      - Ledgers, 1862-71 (Box 44h, Folder 738)
      - Index to 1871-76 (Box 44, Folder 739)
      - Ledgers, 1871-81 (Box 44i, Folder 740-741)
      - Ledgers, 1871-81 (Box 44j, Folder 741)
      - Cashbook [individual pages], 1862 (Box 44, Folder 742)
      - Cashbooks [daybooks], 1862-81 (Box 44k, Folder 743)
      - Cashbooks [daybooks], 1862-81 (Box 44l, Folder 744)
      - Cashbooks [daybooks], 1862-81 (Box 44m, Folder 745)
      - Cashbooks [daybooks], 1862-81 (Box 44n, Folder 746)
      - Cashbooks [daybooks], 1862-81 (Box 44o, Folder 747)